http://www.rachelburklund.com/privacy-policy

Blog
Privacy policy Rachel Burklund Designs has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your privacy. We will not sell, rent, or distribute your name, e-mail address or other identifiable information to any third party. Please check back periodically as our privacy policy may change from time to time. Information Collection & Use To provide you the best possible products and services, we will request specific personal information when you register on rachelburklund.com and when you make a purchase, any personal information collected on RB Designs is knowingly and voluntarily provided by customers and visitors to our site. At registration, we collect your name, shipping and billing addresses, telephone numbers, and e-mail address in order to deliver your orders promptly and to the proper location. We use your e-mail address to send you two emails following a purchase. The first confirms that your order was received, and provides an itemized order summary with your order number. The second e-mail confirms that your order has shipped and provides you with a UPS tracking number so that you can determine the status of your order. Please note that should any of your items be special order, out-of-stock or discontinued, you will receive an additional email after your order confirmation specifying the specific status of each item in question. If necessary, we may contact you by telephone to resolve any issues concerning your order. When you make a purchase at rachelburklund.com you will be immediately directed to Paypal. Paypal has the strongest security on the Internet. RB Designs uses Paypal as the main source for all transactions. We do not use or store any of your credit card information; all of this information goes directly through Paypal. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to assure that all of the information you have submitted is encrypted and transmitted safely over the Internet. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your shopping cart. Your name and password are used to verify that you are a registered customer and prevent anyone else who may have access to your computer from ordering in your name without your express permission. Any email that you may send to us or any correspondences are strictly confidential and are not distributed to any partner or third party. Any information you provide will be used to:   1. Improve upon and personalize the Web site content and services to enhance your shopping experience;  2. Better our customer service; and  3. Contact you about Web site updates, special offers, new products and services. Security Protecting your order information is one of our highest priorities. RB Designs makes every effort to protect your online order information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, an encryption technology that works with every browser so that your personal information cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. The checkout and confirmation areas of RB Designs are secured using SSL technology. This technology is the most advanced security technology available today and ensures that your personal data is never sent over the Internet unencrypted.Payment We accept Stripe as our only form of payment. Stripe uses the strongest security available on the Internet. It is also one of the most trusted source for transferring money online. Sales Tax Domestic taxes, USA- Sales tax is applicable on orders shipped to addresses in the state of Washington. Sales tax is 10.5%, and is based on tax from all major cities in Washington. WA State requires that we charge a sales tax on the full amount of the order. Charges shipping are considered part of the product, by law these charges must be included when sales tax is calculated. International- all duties and taxes are the recipient's obligation. The recipient will be required to pay the duty or VAT upon delivery. Due to import duty valuation adjustments and currency valuations, we are unable to provide an estimate for duty or VAT. If you have any questions please email rb@rachelburklund.com for more details.Contact If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with RB Designs, please contact: RB Designs117 E. Louisa St.Number 126Seattle, WA 98102rb@rachelburklund.com
Back to Top
Rachel Burklund Designs 2014 Terms & Conditions: Privacy Policy
